Play the song of this, there was this
subscribe button, there was
abuse Khan and virus Khan, thank
you, hello, hello
friends, welcome to my channel,
travel government, and today I am going to
Kolkata International
Airport to solve this problem, my immigration
and security checking is all complete, I have
boarding pass
and passport with me,
I am ready now, I have also applied Dravid
and I will be
chicken in a while, so this is International
Distraction Island, so I will
meet you in Thailand and tell you, and one
interesting thing is that before you reach Ireland,
all your information will be done here,
so comment, this is
after insurance
and hotel booking, everything will be done, so
what will be the security checking in Ireland, everything of
yours will be done in India itself, security check, everything has been done, so guys,
I would like to do one thing, first move into the
country,
clear all the documents
[Music]
15909 of bird, ok, bye, next, see
you in Thailand, turn on, turn off, turn off, turn off
[Music]
that a
[Praise]
[Music]
Ajay Ko
According to do it, on
Thursday
morning, Lord
Lut Matric, I am
feeling quite relieved
that the
check-in was as soon as possible.
Good morning friends, I have just reached the
island, I have landed and am
going for the arrival of the
mark herbal, as you
will add in Thailand, your documents will be verified,
your decorum, as soon as you plan to go to Thailand,
your documents will be
verified, which is the I-Pass, after that, only
after the file path I-Pass is verified,
now I will go to the Bijwan rally, so
Ajay Ko,
then I too, who is a novel religion,
one, calendar traveling has become a little different, like
before, I remember that two years back when
I came, it was very simple and smooth that
some document checks are
in the direct vaginal section, I have applied for the visa
and the
influence of the planet,
I have just written that
after this I will talk to you,
welcome to Bangkok, so brother, Bank Of
My official entry has been made and now I am going to
take my Bich Bich film so
this song will also be a great time and we will have a lot of
fun
and now we will definitely give you a glimpse of the night life of Bangkok
and stay connected with me
on Travel Sarkar channel please
subscribe comment and say
that I came by Air Asia flight, just now they
told me that there is a package in number six so number six
66 yes this Rakhi number where is my bag, if
something is needed then there is a conveyor belt
that we took this bag at Kolkata airport
but I did 20 kg
which is the allowed 20 kg with the ticket
and
this is our bag today
that we are in
Thailand Bangkok and my bank
is vitamin A grateful and from here I am telling you, do
n't believe me, but it has already been done for
an update I am telling you here that
first of all you will
come here and your
statement will be checked, here in one place the
last passport and
that passport will be checked,
after this now you will have to fill in the travel card for the flight and
that will also be
checked  After this,
after your documents are verified there,
you have to go straight for visa on arrival. Now,
in Designer Oil,
if you go to this channel, there is a
maximum line there, that is the general
line. Next to it, there is a pass client
where your fast documents are
not checked. There is less crowd, you have to pay Rs. 2208 there
and Rs.
2082 is the general line,
so you have to cross the line
and the
documents are a little less. If you
see this, I was not asked for hotel bookings
and
[Sangeet]
that Meera's return ticket has been checked. I have a
version. I will tell you further
where I am and Manjari. I will block her for that. I am
not going back to India from the melting point. So first of all,
Bangkok to Bangkok, superhit.
Now, cover the pan with photo dried and cigarettes.
Then I have a plan for the second hour. So,
100 is cool here. Your number one is I
pass number to your tech on
[Sangeet]
phone number three arrested by  President
khan9 obviously
I am looting,
you can check your hotel bookings as well, I had
not seen Santosh Yadav in the hotel but
you can check those hotel bookings as well
and so all these things have to be taken care of, there is
no need to worry about come Dana, both of them are too
senior, if
I look at their office at the airport,
long queues have started forming, so I am also getting
trapped, wing in bank of lord
of tourists
is 140 pack,
hello friends, thank you,
so I will talk to you more in future, I will meet you with
new updates, or right now I am going to
check my hotel
in Sukhunvit, so right now I am a
lover, there will not be another one, that is why I will
wait for some time, after that we will
see, so I will meet everyone as soon as possible, the
patients on